chevychasebank.com 2002-12-06

# Chevy Chase Bank - Privacy

**Chevy Chase Bank Family of Companies Privacy Pledge**

**Newsletter articles:**  
Privacy: Protecting This Valuable Asset.  
Opting Out: Removing Your Name From Mail Solicitation Lists.  

At Chevy Chase Bank, we have a long history of respecting our customers' expectation of privacy regarding personal financial information. We value the trust you place in us to protect your personal information. While new technologies have dramatically changed the way information is gathered, used and stored, preserving customer trust and the confidentiality of personal information at Chevy Chase Bank remain core objectives. This is our pledge to our customers: 

  1. We have developed strong security measures to protect customer privacy. We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information. 
  2. The nonpublic personal customer information we collect includes information we receive from applications or other loan and account forms submitted to the Bank. 
  3. We only share customer information concerning your transactions and experience within the Chevy Chase Bank family of companies (the Bank), which includes our mortgage, securities, trust and insurance affiliates. The Chevy Chase Bank family of companies includes: Chevy Chase Bank, Chevy Chase Financial Services Corporation, Chevy Chase Mortgage Company, B.F. Saul Mortgage Company, ASB Capital Management, Inc., Chevy Chase Title Company, Chevy Chase Trust Company, and the Consumer Finance Corporation. This sharing of information is intended only to facilitate the servicing of our customers' accounts and to offer financial products and services we believe would be beneficial to our customers. 
  4. We share other customer information with service providers who assist us in servicing customer accounts and preparing and/or delivering Bank services and products to our customers. Examples of such service providers include check printers, check verification services, mortgage payment facilitators and credit reporting agencies. 
  5. We also share limited customer information with our joint marketing partners, which include insurance companies, allowing us to offer a variety of financial products and services we endorse and believe you may find beneficial. The information we share is limited to information provided on applications. Under all sharing arrangements, the Bank requires its service providers and marketing partners to keep such information confidential and prohibits them from disclosing such information to anyone for any other purpose. **_We do not, and will not, share customer information with non-financial companies for the purpose of allowing them to market their products and services to our customers._**
  6. We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers to any other third parties, except as permitted or required by law. 
  7. We obtain only limited medical information required to initiate a customer's request for insurance products or services. In those instances, we will forward that information to the insurance company only to facilitate obtaining the insurance product for which you apply. We will not otherwise disclose such information to anyone unless authorized by the customer or required by law, and we will not use this information for any other purpose. 
  8. If you decide to close your account(s) or your account(s) become inactive, we will continue to adhere to the Bank's current privacy policies and practices. 

We believe it is important to make clear to our customers how information is being used at Chevy Chase Bank, the benefits such use provides, and the protections put in place against unauthorized access and use. We respect your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information, and we appreciate the opportunity to do business with you.

**Newsletter articles:**  
Privacy: Protecting This Valuable Asset.  
Opting Out: Removing Your Name From Mail Solicitation Lists.
